buddymedia.com 2013-03-24

# Privacy Policy | Buddy Media

Effective Date: September 1, 2011

Buddy Media, Inc. ("Buddy Media") respects your concerns about privacy. This Online Privacy Policy applies to personal information we collect on buddymedia.com (the "Site"). The Online Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we collect, how we use the information, with whom we share it and the choices you can make about our use of the information. We also describe the measures we take to protect the security of the information and how you can contact us about our privacy practices.

Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section:

  * Information We Collect
  * How We Use the Information We Collect
  * Sharing of Information
  * Your Rights and Choices
  * Data Transfers
  * Protection of Personal Information
  * Links to Other Websites
  * Updates to Our Online Privacy Policy
  * How to Contact Us

#### Information We Collect

We may obtain certain personal information you submit to us through our Site, including contact information (such as name, postal address, email address and telephone number). In addition, we offer visitors to our Site various services, which we may change from time to time. We may ask you to submit certain personal information so we can provide you with these services.

When you visit our Site, information may be collected through automated technologies such as cookies, web server logs and web beacons. A "cookie" is a file that websites send to a visitor's computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor's browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A "web beacon," also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. The information collected using these tools may include your IP address, browser characteristics, operating system, the address of the web page that referred you to our Site, dates and times of Site visits, the language your system uses, and the country and time zone in which your device is located. These technologies permit the collection of "clickstream data," which may include a log of content you access while browsing a website.

On our Site, we use third-party web analytics services, such as those of Google Analytics. The service providers that administer these services may use technologies such as cookies, web server logs and web beacons to help analyze how visitors arrive at and interact with the Site. The information collected through these means (including IP address) is disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers. To learn more about the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, [click here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

#### How We Use the Information We Collect

We may use the information we obtain about you to:

  * Provide, administer and communicate with you about products, services, events and promotions (including by sending you marketing communications); 
  * process, evaluate and respond to your requests, inquiries and comments; 
  * operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; performing market research; determining and managing the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing; analyzing our products, services and websites; and administering our websites); 
  * protect against and prevent fraud, unauthorized activities, claims and other liabilities; and 
  * comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies and terms. 

We also may use the information in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection. 

#### Sharing of Information

We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information we collect on our Site, except as described here. We may share the information with our service providers who perform services on our behalf. These service providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. 

In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process (such as a court order), (ii) in response to a request by law enforcement authorities, (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or (iv) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. We also reserve the right to transfer personal information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided to us on our Site in a manner that is consistent with our Online Privacy Policy.

#### Your Rights and Choices

We offer you certain choices about how we communicate with you and what information we collect from you. You may contact us as described in the How to Contact Us section below to update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists or submit other requests.

#### Data Transfers

We may transfer the personal information we collect about you to countries other than the country in which the information was originally collected. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy and in accordance with applicable law.

If you are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”) or Switzerland, we comply with applicable legal requirements providing adequate protection for the transfer of personal information to countries outside the EEA or Switzerland. Buddy Media is certified under the Safe Harbor privacy framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce, European Commission and Switzerland regarding the collection, storage, use, transfer and other processing of personal data transferred from the EEA or Switzerland to the U.S. Click here to view our Safe Harbor Privacy Policy 

#### Protection of Personal Information

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.

#### Links to Other Websites

Our Site may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These websites may operate independently from Buddy Media. The websites may have their own Privacy Policies or policies, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites or pages containing content hosted by other websites. To the extent such websites are not owned or controlled by Buddy Media, we are not responsible for the websites' content, any use of the websites, or the privacy practices of the websites.

#### Updates to Our Online Privacy Policy

This Online Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices. We will post the updated version on this page, and indicate at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.

#### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Online Privacy Policy, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by:

  * Using the [Contact Us](http://www.buddymedia.com/contact) form on the Site
  * Calling us at 646-380-7300 or 888-90-Buddy
  * Writing to us at:  
Buddy Media, Inc.  
Attention: Steven Oh  
155 6th Avenue  
12th Floor  
New York, NY 10013
